University of Connecticut 1998.0380
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, undated, 1926-1935
  - 1934-1935
    - Hypes, James L. [Sociology] (Box 17:, Folder 378)
    - I - K (Box 17:, Folder 379)
    - Kelly, E. Lowell (Box 17:, Folder 380)
    - Kessel, Marcel [English] (Box 17:, Folder 381)
    - King, Olcott F. [Trustee] (Box 17:, Folder 382)
    - L (Box 17:, Folder 383)
    - Land Grant College Association (Box 17:, Folder 384)
    - Longley, Raymond I. [Comptroller] (Box 17:, Folder 385)
    - M (Box 17:, Folder 386)
    - Manchester, Harry G. [Trustee] (Box 17:, Folder 387)
    - McEvoy, Judge Frank P. (Box 17:, Folder 388)
    - Military Correspondence (Box 17:, Folder 389)
    - Moore, Edmund A. [History and Government] (Box 17:, Folder 390)
    - N (Box 17:, Folder 391)
    - National Archery Tournament (Box 17:, Folder 392)
    - National Grange Convention (Box 17:, Folder 393)
    - Newton, Howard D. [Chemistry] (Box 17:, Folder 394)
    - Noble, Daniel E. [Radio] (Box 17:, Folder 395)
    - North Atlantic Regional Public Speaking Contest [F.F.A., 21 September 1934] (Box 17:, Folder 396)
    - O (Box 17:, Folder 397)
    - Oliver, Bernard J. [Assistant Comptroller] (Box 18:, Folder 398)
    - P (Box 18:, Folder 399)
    - Payne, Fernandus [Indiana University] (Box 18:, Folder 400)
    - Pinches, Harold E. [Agricultural Engineering] (Box 18:, Folder 401)
    - Post Office, Establishment of (Box 18:, Folder 402)
    - Prospective Students (Box 18:, Folder 403)
    - Q - R (Box 18:, Folder 404)
    - Registrar (Box 18:, Folder 405)
    - S (includes Speeches) (Box 18:, Folder 406)
    - Salary study (Box 18:, Folder 407)
    - Scholarship Loan Committee (Box 18:, Folder 408)
    - Scholarship Standing Committee (Box 18:, Folder 409)
    - Slate, William L. [Director, Experiment Station] (Box 18:, Folder 410)
    - Spencer, Samuel R. [Trustee] (Box 18:, Folder 411)
    - State Universities Association (Box 18:, Folder 412)
    - Student Government, Committee on (Box 18:, Folder 413)
    - Student Senate (Box 18:, Folder 414)
    - T (Box 18:, Folder 415)
    - Tercentenary Celebration (Box 18:, Folder 416)
    - U - W (Box 18:, Folder 417)
    - Waugh, Albert E. [Economics] (Box 18:, Folder 418)
    - White, George C. [Dean, School of Agriculture] (Box 18:, Folder 419)
    - Wood, Walter C. [Trustee] (Box 18:, Folder 420)
    - X - Z (Box 18:, Folder 421)